Finding Aid for Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers
Clarke Historical Library
- Nellie May Davis Finley Family Papers.
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: G. McEwen,January 8, 18, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. C. R. Prine,January 9, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Mrs. Mary Wright Collins,January 11, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Nellie McMurtrie?,January 12, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: Doc, Pa,January 12, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Earl,January 13, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy Ruff,January 18, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,January 19, 30, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. J. E. Helmer,January 19, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Uncle Phil, Aunt Louie Hartung,January 23, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bessie Thompson,January 24, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,January 30, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: Lizzie, Gib,January 31, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: Edward,February 2, 24, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron and Nellie Finley,February 13-14, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron and Nellie Finley,February 20, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,February 9, 18, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,February 23, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,February 2, 9, 16, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,February 23, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: George Marshall,February 2, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: E. G. "Pa' Finley,February 4, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. M. A. Merritt,February 5, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Wilson Davis,February 17, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: Aunt Florence Finley,February 18, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nellie McMurtrie,February 2, 23, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: The Shermans,February 23, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,March 2, 9, 16, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,March 24, 30, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Flossie Foster,March 11, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,March 16, 24, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron S., Nellie Finley,March 14, 21, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grace,March 14, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: S.M. Eaton,March 16, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: E. G. "Pa" Finley,March 16, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gertrude, Clarence, and Elmer H. Abbott,March 16, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,March 17, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: C. E. Finley,March 21, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,March 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron S., Nellie Finley,April 1, 10, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron S., Nellie Finley,April 13, 20, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron S., Nellie Finley,April 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bessie,April 2, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,April 2, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Fay,April 5, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,April 5, 13, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,April 20, 25, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,April 28, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Ina Stone,April 5, 24, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Inez A. McNeil,April 6, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Philena Corbett,April 7, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: E. G. "Pa" Finley,April 13, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Amy Ruff,April 14-15, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry E. Davis,April 15, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,April 18, 20, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,April 26-27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. L. L. Herrick,April 20, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Philena,April 21, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Adelie?,April 21, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ida,April 24, 30, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Aunt Thera, Aunt Louie,April 26, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: N. G. McMurtrie,April 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: E. G. "Pa" Finley,April 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Unidentified,April 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,May 4, 11, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,May 18, 25, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Auntie Scurrah,May 6, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nellie G. McMurtrie,May 6, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Grandma Barnes, Aunt Bessie,May 8, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron S., Nellie, and baby Theron Finley,May 10, 14, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron S., Nellie, and baby Theron Finley,May 28, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry and Zoe Davis,May 11, 18, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: E. G. "Pa" Finley,May 18, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: C. W. Yost,May 24, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Minnie M. Sherman,May 31, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,June 1, 7, 15, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,June 22, 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Nellie, Theron S., and baby Theron Finley,June 5, 8, 25, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bessie,June 12, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: E. G. "Pa" Finley,June 15, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry E. Davis,June 19, 26, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry E. Davis,June 28, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nellie McMurtrie,June 22, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ida,June 26, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mary A. Merritt,June 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Bessie,July 1, 5, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron S., Nellie, and Theron W. Finley,July 3, 19, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron S., Nellie, and Theron W. Finley,July 25, 31, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S., Nellie, and Theron W. Finley From: Aunt Philena,July 6, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,July 6, 13, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,July 20, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Gertie,July 7, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Gertie,July 13, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sybil,July 14, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Fay,July 14, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Della Burgess,July 18, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,July 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sylvia,July 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nellie G. McMurtrie,July 29, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,July 29, 31, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harrietta,August [no day], 1913 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Addie,August 2, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,August 3, 10, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,August 11, 19, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,August 25, 31, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: E. G. "Pa" Finley,August 4, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry and Zoe Davis,August 5, 26, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Florence,August 7, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron S., Nellie, and Theron W. Finley,August 8, 16, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron S., Nellie, and Theron W. Finley,August 22, 28, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edna,August 10, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Thera,August 17, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Inez A. McNeil,August 25, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna, Alice B.,September 1, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Aunt Philena,September 1, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: E. G. "Pa" Finley,September 2, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Nellie G. McMurtrie,September 2, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: NDF, Theron Wilson Finley,September 5, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,September 7, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,September 7, 15, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,September 21, 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mrs. Helmer,September 8, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley, Theron W. Finley,September 11, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry E. Davis,September 16, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Elmer, Clarence, and Gertrude Abbott,September 20-21, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Bessie Thompson,September 25, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Fred McMurtrie,September 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Fay,October 1, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edna,October 5, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,October 5, 19, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,October 26, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ida,October 6, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,October 8, 12, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,October 28, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis, Aunt Nellie,October 11, 17, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis, Aunt Nellie,October 18, 23, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis, Aunt Nellie,October 24, 31, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,October 12, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Ethel,October 12, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sybil,October 12, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mary A. Merritt,October 17, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,October 19, 28, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harrietta,October 20, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Earl,October 26, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - Correspondence to: NDF c/o Harmond Ruff From: E. G. "Pa" Finley,October 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: E. G. "Pa" Finley,October 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: C. D. White,October 30, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Correspondence to:Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis,November 2, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Anna,November 3, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Edna Howard,November 3, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy Ruff,November 10, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Gran Ma Finley,November 12, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna, Aunt Philena,November 12-13, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry E. Davis,November 14, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harmond and Amy Ruff,November 15, 21, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jeanne Destree,November 16, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Della Burgess,November 23, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ida,December 7, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Anna,December 11, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,December 12, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Correspondence to: Anna From: Gertie,December 15, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy Ruff,December 16, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mother, Inez, and Anna,December 16, 26, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: S. M. Eaton,December 21, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry E. Davis,December 23, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sybil,December 29, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Loretta Dain,December 27, 1913 (Box 7, Folder 180)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ina Stone,January 22, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to: Mama From: NDF,1914? (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. T. S. Finley From: Michigan Mutual Life Insurance Company,January 2, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis, Aunt Nellie,January 5, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis, Aunt Nellie,January 28, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Philena,January 5, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Philena, with Poem and Picture by Alice Blanch Corbett,January 30, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jeanne Destree,January 5, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harrietta Helmer, January 11, 1914; with Agreement between Theron S. Finley and Harmond A. Ruff, November 1, 1913,January 1, 1913; November 11, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Amy,January 12, 1913 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. T. S. Finley From: Harmond A. Ruff, January 11, 1914; with Lumberyard Receipts, November 1913,November 1913; January 11, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sybil,January 25, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Alice Prine,January 31, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Fay,February 8, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: "We Three Howards?",February 11, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy,undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Bessie Thompson,February 14, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: H. A. Ruff, February 16, 1914; with Lumberyard Receipts, January 1914,January 1914; February 16, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Della B.,February 21, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mama,March 9, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mama, Papa; with a program, undatedMarch 22, 1914; undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: The RuffsMarch 1, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Harry,March 1, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: W.; March 15, 1914; with Miscellaneous Receipts, undated,March 15, 1914; undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Philean,March 21, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence to: NDF, TSF, and Baby From: Harry, Wilson, and Zoe Davis,March 21, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Jeanne S. Destree,March 23, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sybil,March 29, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence to: NDF, From: May B. Hawes, Eva L. King,March 31, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence to: NDF, All From: Harmond, Richard, and Amy Ruff, April 27, 1914; with Miscellaneous Receipts, undated,April 27, 1914; undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence to: NDF, All From: Amy Ruff and Family,April 3, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. T. S. Finley From: Michigan Mutual Life Insurance Company, April 3, 1914; Death Notice from same company, January 21, 1915,April 3, 1914; January 21, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mama,April 7, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence to: NDF, All From: Harry Davis,April 26, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sybil,May 10, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sybil,May 31, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence to: Mr. and Mrs. Theron S. Finley From: Mr. and Mrs. McEwen,May 13, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Aunt Philena,May 15, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna, with Swatches of Material,undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Harry Davis,May 24, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Zoe, Wilson Davis,May 24, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Zoe, Wilson Davis,May 24, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence to: Parents From: Harry,May 24, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: H. A. Ruff,May 24, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Amy Ruff, with Miscellaneous Receipts,May 24, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence to: Girls (Ida, Anna) From: NDF,May 24, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Ida,undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sybil,June 23, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sybil,June 27, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Theron, Nellie Finley, with Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings,June 1, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence to: Parents, Aunt (Mrs. W. H. Davis) From: Harry, Zoe, and Wilson Davis,June 8, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence to: Mrs. W. H. Davis From: Anna,June 9, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Della B.,June 14, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: George M.,June 14, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry Davis,undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Harry and Zoe Davis,June 22, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Amy Ruff,June 27, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sybil,July 2, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Sybil, with Wedding Invitation,July 12, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harrietta Helmer,July 13, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence to: Theron S. Finley From: H. A. Ruff, with Miscellaneous Receipts,July 15, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Amy Ruff,July 14, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence to: Parents and All From: Harry Davis,July 14, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Harry Davis,July 19, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mama, Papa,July 24, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence to: Aunt Mattie From: Anna,July 2, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Anna,July 29, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence to: Aunt Mattie From: Anna, Alice B.,July 20, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Fay,July 30, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mama, Papa,August 11, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Mama, Papa,August 21, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence to: Father, Aunt From: Harry Davis, with Map and Directions,August 24, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence to: Parents and All From: Harry, Dave,August 4, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence to: Parents and All From: Harry Davis,August 5, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence to: Parents and All From: Harry Davis,August 22, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence to: Parents and All From: Harry Davis,August 20, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence to: Father, Aunt From: Harry Davis,August 25, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence to: Father, Aunt From: Harry Davis,August 31, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry Davis,August 31, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Harry Davis,August 22, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence to: NDF and All From: Zoe, Harry Davis,August 17, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Harry Davis,August 25, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: May L. Carson,August 17, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence to: NDF From: Earl (Cousin),August 30, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 84)